{
    "id": "25441706881f4433b061a608d124454d",
    "title": "For Or To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We stopped at the pub …………….. a drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce5c2d0d2052439db8f41b656cf00acb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He stopped the car ……………… drop her off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "99143d156737413597d456328c12a81c"
        },
        {
            "question": "They stopped ………………… get some rest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72a75c75567c4dcb8289e45f7d69538b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We use thermometers ……………….. measure temperatures.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5f3b3a6ba64444fa0479370d879f41a"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was hard ………………… finish on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30af09cb971441e3852feacf969f43ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to his office ………………… a talk with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8284b34c2af4456d8f8f6350e0264703"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was sent to prison ………………. stealing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ead9c089e7184a79891c829f7d033490"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was angry with me …………………. lying to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3f06ed563fa4a2cba7cdcd6a99fdd46"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to Mexico ……………….. meet my brother who lives there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7fd2e5e440647bc8d69e2b31a6244c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "A barometer is used ………………… measuring pressure.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9eaa8c5504114fc7ae46c5549d3eb333"
        }
    ]
}